export const questions = [
  {
    question: "Who/What is Xron Trix?!",
    command: "whois xrontrix --verbose",
    answer:
      "I'm a front-end developer with a passion for developing full-stack applications.",
  },
  {
    question: "What I actually do?",
    command: "man xrontrix",
    answer:
      "I'm a front-end developer with a passion for developing full-stack applications.",
  },
  {
    question: "Skills? Experience?",
    command: "info xrontrix",
    answer:
      "I'm a front-end developer with a passion for developing full-stack applications.",
  },
  {
    question: "Where I'm from?",
    command: "whereis xrontrix",
    answer: "I live in the United States.",
  },
  {
    question: "What is my current role?",
    command: "which role",
    answer:
      "I'm a front-end developer with a passion for developing full-stack applications.",
  },
  {
    question: "Strengths and weaknesses?",
    command: "describe --strengths --weakness",
    answer:
      "My strengths include my ability to develop full-stack applications and my passion for front-end development.",
  },
  {
    question: "Favorite technologies?",
    command: "which techs",
    answer:
      "I'm a front-end developer with a passion for developing full-stack applications.",
  },
  {
    question: "Which Operating System do I use?",
    command: "which os",
    answer: "Windows 10",
  },
  {
    question: "Favorite tools?",
    command: "which tools",
    answer: "I use Visual Studio Code as my primary code editor.",
  },
  {
    question: "Favorite websites?",
    command: "which websites",
    answer: "I love to browse websites and learn new things.",
  },
  {
    question: "Hobbies?",
    command: "what hobbies",
    answer: "I love to read books and watch movies.",
  },
  {
    question: "Favorite books?",
    command: "which books",
    answer: "I love reading books about history, philosophy, and science.",
  },
  {
    question: "Favorite movies?",
    command: "which movies",
    answer: "I love watching movies about adventure, romance, and comedy.",
  },
];
